http://www.ecis.org/privacy-policy/

loading...
Website Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last updated: Monday 9 November, 2020
ECIS Limited (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates https://www.ecis.org (the “Site”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the minimal collection and use of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, address, gender, email address and mobile phone number.
Financial Information
Where applicable, payments are securely processed via a third party company, Stripe, and as such we do not store any of your payment card details on our system.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of benefit to you.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site.
This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyse this data, allowing us to improve our site, and thereby enhancing your online experience.
Cookies
Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of Monday 20 July, 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Website Visitor Agreement
Click here to see our Website Visitor Agreement
Global Headquarters
24 Greville Street
London EC1N 8SS
Tel. +44(0)20 7824 7040
Email: ecis@ecis.org
PAYMENTS
PRIVACY POLICY
CONTACT US
BOARD LOGIN
ABOUT ECISFounded in 1965, ECIS is a non-profit
global membership organisation that supports schools. ECIS was the first educational collaborative to serve Europe and has grown into a leading global association. Our historical foundation has always been to provide thought leadership and the ECIS tradition of sustainable, caring, and inclusive learning will forever be our legacy.
Together, we create a movement
to change the way the
world learns.
